## Khoa Pham

Senior Front-end Developer

## Profile

With background of computer science and over 6+ years of experience with web application development. My passion is to write clean code and develop good UX. I like working on the front-end because it helps delivering direct experience to users.

## Experience

### Senior Application Engineer - Joyn.co

01/2018 - Present

Work with Nike Accelerator start-up team to build application that helps everyone to connect and enjoy fitness anytime and anywhere.

## UI Developer II, Healthsparq - Cambia Health Solutions 12/2016 - 01/2018

Work with talented Healsparq team to build products that reinvent healthcare industries for a better and transparent healthcare.

### Senior Front-end Developer, Seastar.io

03/2015 - 12/2016

Lead of front-end development to design and create intuitive web application for Seastar dashboard using EmberJS, D3.js, Go, Cassandra.

#### Web Application Engineer, The Program PDX

10/2014 - 03/2015

Take technical ownership of projects and be responsible for architecting and developing complex digital solutions using full-stack technologies like Rails, Postgres, Ember, Backbone, NodeJS, ThreeJS, and D3.js.

## Web Developer, Sincerely Truman (Epipheo)

08/2011 - 10/2014

Lead of front-end to develop complex websites and applications. Build highly customized Wordpress themes and Wordpress plugins.

# Labs Technician and Server Operations, Portland State University 06/2010 - 08/2012

Work with server operations team to mange Portland State datacenter. Support staffs and students at PSU for computer software and hardware.

## Education

# **BS. Computer Science, Portland State University** 2009 - 2012

**Advanced Computer Science Program, Vietnam National University** 2007 - 2009

## Contact

⊠ khoa.pham@me.com

www.khoapham.me

@pmkhoa

github.com/pmkhoa

## Tech Skills

#### Front-end

React, Redux, EmberJS,
GraphQL, Apollo, D3,
ThreeJS, TweenMax, SASS.

#### **Programming Languages**

Javascript, Go, PHP, Ruby, Java, HTML.

#### **Database**

Postgres, Graphql, MySQL.

#### **Frameworks**

Ember, Rails, ExpressJS, Wordpress, Go Web API.

### **DevOps**

AWS, Lamda, Linux Server, Docker.

### **Work Tools**

Vim, Tmux, Git, Sketch, Slack.

### UX

Sketch, sharp eyes for design.

## Hobbies

Practice meditation

Learn latest technology

Cooking

Play with my kids